<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ImmiGreat</string>
    <string name="welcomeStr">Welcome!</string> <!--English-->
    <string name="welcomeStr1">स्वागत हे!</string> <!--Hindi-->
    <string name="welcomeStr2">欢迎!</string> <!--Chinese Simplified-->
    <string name="welcomeStr3">أهلا بك!</string> <!--Arabic-->

    <!--Big buttons on main menu-->
    <string name="menuButton1Str">Public Transportation</string>
    <string name="menuButton2Str">Laws</string>
    <string name="menuButton3Str">Healthcare</string>

    <!--Headings-->
    <string name="lawsHeadingStr">Laws</string>
    <string name="transportationHeadingStr">Transportation</string>

    <!--Button labels and subheadings-->
    <string name="lawsEducationHeadingStr">Education</string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingHeadingStr">Driving</string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingApplyingLicenseHeadingStr">Applying for a Class D License</string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingForeignPolicyHeadingStr">Foreign Policy</string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingCellPhoneHeadingStr">Cell Phone Usage</string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingJOLHeadingStr">Junior Operator License Requirements</string>
    <string name="lawsKnowYourRightsHeadingStr">Know Your Rights</string>
    <string name="lawsDiscriminationHeadingStr">Antidiscrimination</string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareHeadingStr">Healthcare</string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcarePageNewArrivalsStr">What Do I Do First?</string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcarePageSpecialConcernsStr">Specific Groups and Special Health Concerns</string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcarePageFactsheetsStr">Factsheets and Other Resources</string>
    <string name="lawsPublicChargeHeadingStr">Public Charge</string>
    <string name="lawsPublicChargePageOtherInformationStr">General Information</string>
    <string name="lawsPublicChargePageFactsheetsStr">Factsheets</string>

    <string name="transportationStayingLocalHeadingStr">Staying Local?</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarHeadingStr">Going Further Afield?</string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityHeadingStr">Is accessibility a concern?</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayStr">Subway</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwaySchedulesStr">Schedules, Routes, and Maps</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayFaresStr">Fares</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayEtiquetteStr">Etiquette</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayAccessibilityStr">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayLanguageServicesStr">Language Services</string>
    <string name="transportationBusStr">Bus Routes</string>
    <string name="transportationBusScheduleStr">Schedules and Routes</string>
    <string name="transportationBusFaresStr">Fares</string>
    <string name="transportationBusEtiquetteStr">Etiquette</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryStr">Ferry Routes</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerrySchedulesStr">Schedules</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryFaresStr">Fares</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryNavigatingFerryDocksStr">Navigating Ferry Docks</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDuringtheTripStr">During the Trip</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailStr">Commuter Rail</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailSchedulesStr">Schedules and Routes</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailFaresStr">Fares</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingCommuterRailStationsStr">Navigating Commuter Rail Stations</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailOntheTrainStr">On the Train</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailAccessibilityStr">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityTheRIDEStr">The RIDE</string>


    <!--Content strings-->
    <string name="error404PageContentStr">ERROR</string>
    <string name="lawsEducationPageContentStr"> 1. Required hours of attendance at public school \n\t
        i. Every minor subject to laws pertaining to public schools is required to attend said schools/courses
        in the town of his employment for no less than 4 hours per week. \n\t ii. Attendance of minors
        who are required to attend continuation schools, and are temporarily out of work, are required
        to attend said school for no less than 20 hours per week. \n2. Compulsory education laws \n\t
        i. Children aged 7 and older are required to attend school, unless deemed mentally or physically
        unable to attend/ have immediate needs at home \n\t ii. In Massachusetts, individuals are required
        to attend school if they are under the age of 16 years. \n\t\t a. 14-16 year olds who have completed
        6th grade and hold a permit for employment in domestic service or a farm, is regularly employed
        a minimum of 6 hours per day, and has written permission of superintendent to engage in non-wage
        earning employment at home are allowed to not attend school \n\t iii. Homeschool provisions approval
        is up to the superintendent and/or school committee - review curriculum, evaluation methods,
        textbooks, etc.\n3. Federal Law \n\t i. States and school districts are required to provide all
        children in the U.S. with an equal access to a basic public education regardless of citizenship
        or immigration status. \n4. No refusing \n\t i. No school committee shall refuse a school-age
        child with a disability admission or continued attendance in a public school without prior
        written approval of the department and without complying with state and federal requirements
        for discipling students with disabilities
    </string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingApplyingPageContentStr">1. Required documents: proof of U.S. citizenship
        or lawful presence, Social Security number, and Massachusetts residency. \n\t a. Original documents,
        no photocopies or laminated documents \n\t b. One document cannot be used to prove more than one
        requirement \n\t c. Lawful presence: legally living in the U.S. according to federal immigration
        laws \n\t\t i. Non-U.S. citizens who are working, studying, or living temporarily in the U.S.
        might have temporary lawful presence that varies in length \n\t\t ii. For U.S. citizens: valid,
        unexpired U.S. passport or certified copy of U.S. birth certificate \n\t\t iii. For permanent
        residents: valid permanent resident card (green card) iv. For non-U.S. citizens: valid verifiable
        immigration documents and proof of grant of a legal stay in the U.S. for at least 12 months
        \n\t d. Social Security Number (SSN): must have a valid SSN (9 digit number) to apply for any
        learner\’s permit, driver\’s license, or ID card, bring one of the following: \n\t\t i. SSN card
        (not laminated) \n\t\t ii. W-2 Form - wage and tax statement \n\t\t iii. SSA 1099 Form - tax
        form for individuals who receive social security benefits \n\t\t iv. Pay stub with applicant\'s
        name and full SSN \n\t\t v. SSN denial notice with passport, visa and I-94 \n\t e. Massachusetts
        residency documents: document showing current residential address(2 of the following documents
        for a Real ID, 1 for Standard driver\'s license) \n\t\t i. Massachusetts RMV-issued documents
        \n\t\t\t Ex) Current license, Massachusetts ID card, learner\'s permit, or RMV-issued correspondence
        \n\t\t ii. State/federal/municipal/city/town/country agency-issued documents \n\t\t\t Ex) 1st
        class government-issued mail, medicaid statement, current firearms card, or jury duty summons
        all dated within 60 days \n\t\t iii. Bills \n\t\t\t Ex) Utility bill (electric, telephone, water,
        cable, etc), credit card statement, medical statement, cell phone bill all dated within 60 days
        \n\t\t iv. Lease/Mortgage documents \n\t\t\t Ex) Current lease/mortgage or similar rental contract
        \n\t\t vi. Financial related document \n\t\t\t Ex) Bank statements, SSA statement, school-issued
        documents, insurance related documents \n2. Real ID vs Standard ID \n\t a. From Oct 2020, a Real ID can
        be used to fly within the United States or enter federal buildings \n3. Can start application
        online or start application at the RMV - <a href="https://atlas-myrmv.massdot.state.ma.us/myrmv/_/">https://atlas-myrmv.massdot.state.ma.us/myrmv/_/</a>
    </string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingForeignPolicyPageContentStr">1. Foreign-licensed drivers from another country
        that meet certain requirements* may operate a validly registered motor vehicle in Massachusetts
        for up to 1 year. After 1 year, any non-immigrant visa holder must obtain a Massachusetts
        Driver’s License in order to drive legally in the U.S. \n\t a. *Requirements: at least 16 years of
        age, in possession of a valid driver’s license when operating a motor vehicle, may operate the
        same type of vehicle in which licensed to operate in another country, license must not be suspended
        or revoked,  if foreign license is not in English or doesn’t have an English translation, must
        have an International Driving Permit (IDP), a Translation into English of a Foreign License
        document, or an alternative translation documents that has a photo and English translation
        that closely matches information from an IDP. </string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingJOLPageContentStr">1. Any licensed individual between the ages of 16 ½ and
        18 is a Junior Operator \n2. Individuals are required to be at least 16 years of age before obtaining
        a learner’s permit \n3. Learner’s permits are obtained through the DMV/RMV \n4. Learner’s permit
        holders may drive if they have the learner’s permit while driving and when accompanied by a driver
        who is licensed, at least 21 years of age, has at least one year of driving experience, and is
        occupying the passenger’s seat (seat next to the driver) \n5. Students under the age of 18 applying
        for a license are required to have completed all of the requirements of drivers education: 30 hours of
        classroom education, 12 hours of behind-the-wheel driving, 6 hours of in-car observation, and parent
        attendance at a 2-hour parent class. \n6. After obtaining a Junior Operator License, the teen is prohibited
        from driving with any passengers under the age of 18, excluding any immediate family members, for the
        first 6 months unless accompanied by a licensed driver who is at least 21 years old. \n7. Anyone obtaining
        a Junior Operator License is prohibited from driving between 12:30 a.m. and 5 a.m. unless accompanied
        by a parent or legal guardian.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsKnowYourRightsContentStr"> 1. Individuals have freedom of speech, freedom of religion,
        freedom of assembly, freedom of the press, and the right to petition. \n2. Stopped by Police/Pulled
        over by police \n\t i. You have the right to remain silent. If you wish to exercise this right,
        say so out loud. \n\t ii. If arrested, you have the right to a government-appointed lawyer if
        unable to afford one of your own and the right to make a local phone call. \n\t iii. If police
        are at your door, they may not enter without a warrant signed by a judicial officer that lists
        your address or has your name on it. \n3. Voting in Massachusetts \n\t i. Individuals must be at
        least 18 years of age, a U.S. citizen, meet state’s residency requirements, and registered to
        vote by state’s voter registration deadline in order to vote. \n\t ii. Individuals must be a
        resident of the state - the amount of time you have been a resident does not matter \n\t iii.
        Registration deadline is 20 days before the election - voters can register online, mail, or
        in person at a registration office or the RMV. \n\t iv. Form of identification is required,
        acceptable forms: \n\t\t a. Valid driver’s license \n\t\t b. State issued identification card
        \n\t\t c. Current utility bill \n\t\t d. Bank statement \n\t\t e. Paystub \n\t\t f. Government-issued check
        \n\t\t g. Other government document that has voter’s name and address \n\t v. Automatic registration -
        MA automatically registers eligible individuals through the DMV, division of medical assistance,
        health insurance connector authority, and other agencies that collect reliable citizenship information
        \n\t vi. Online registration - Individuals can visit <a href="https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ovr/">https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ovr/</a>
        to register online
        \n4. Marriage \n\t i. Same sex marriage is legal in all 50 states. \n\t ii. To obtain a marriage
        license, an individual must be at least 18 years of age. Parental consent is required for individuals
        under the age of 18. \n\t iii. Marrying a relative is illegal.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsDiscriminationPageContentStr">1. Federally Assisted Program \n\t i. Prohibits
        discrimination in federally assisted programs - no person in the U.S. can be excluded from,
        denied benefits of, or subject to discrimination under and program that receives federal
        assistance based on their race, color, or national origin (this includes limited proficiency
        in English) \n\t\t a. Examples of federally assisted programs: Child and Adult Care Food Program,
        Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program, Alcohol, Drug Abuse, and Mental Health Services Block
        Grant \n2. Public Accommodation \n\t i. Prohibits making distinction, discrimination or restriction
        in admitting to a place of public accommodation based on race, color, religious beliefs, national
        origin, sex, sexual orientation, disability, or ancestry \n3. State provided services \n\t i. All
        programs, activities and services provided by the state are required to be conducted without
        unlawful discrimination based on race, color, age, gender, ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender
        identity or expression, religion, ancestry, national origin, disability, veteran status, or
        background \n4. Religious Freedom \n\t i. Employers are prohibited from discriminating on the
        basis of religion. \n\t ii. Religious discrimination in rental, sale, and financing of homes
        is prohibited. \n\t iii. School officials can not include religious activities into school
        events, impose their faith on students, require students to read religious texts without a
        secular reason for doing so, display religious symbols without a secular, academic reason, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsDrivingCellPhonePageContentStr">1. In Massachusetts, hand-held cell phone use by
        drivers is banned. If drivers want to talk on the phone while operating a motor vehicle they
        are required to use Bluetooth or another hands-free technology tool.</string>

    <string name="lawsHealthcarePageOverviewStr">All people in Massachusetts, regardless of
        immigration status, have access to some sort of healthcare. For more information on the
        different forms of healthcare and what forms you are eligible for, see below:
    </string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareNewArrivalsHeading1">Preventative and Early Care</string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareNewArrivalsContent1">There are a variety of different ways which can
        be done, but one of the easiest is the
        <a href="https://www.mass.gov/refugee-health-assessment-program-rhap">RHAP (Refugee Health
            Assessment Program).</a> RHAP is a service provided by the Massachusetts Office for
        Refugees and Immigrants, and they work to provide services which are both linguistically and
        culturally appropriate to people who are newly arriving to the country. \n In addition to
        primary assessment services, RHAP provides follow up check ups, immunizations, and referral
        to primary care services. \n \n A second association which offers similar services is the
        <a href="https://www.acf.hhs.gov/orr/programs/preventive-health/about">Refugee Preventative
            Health Program (RHP)</a> through the Office of Refugee Resettlement, provided by the
        federal government.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareNewArrivalsHeading2">Ongoing Care: Refugee Medical Assistance (RMA)
    </string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareNewArrivalsContent2">Individuals who have gained legal refugee
        status or anyone else eligible for Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR) service (determine
        your eligibility <a href="https://www.acf.hhs.gov/orr/about/what-we-do">here</a>) but are
        not eligible for medicaid are entitled to 8 months of Refugee Medical Assistance. RMA
        provides similar benefits to medicaid, but to this specific population. Please note that: \n
        -This 8 month period starts on the date of arrival to the United States, not date of
        entering the program \n -After the 8 months have elapsed, individuals must determine their
        qualified immigrant status to see what healthcare they are eligible for. Learn more about
        qualified immigrant status
        <a href="https://www.nilc.org/issues/economic-support/overview-immeligfedprograms/">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareFactsheetsContent">Some important information on healthcare in
        Massachusetts: \n-HIPAA laws mean that health professionals cannot give away personal
        information about (but not limited to) immigration, and so going to the doctor, the health
        clinic, or the hospital is safe for everyone, and so is applying for public health insurance
        though MassHealth, the Health Connector and Mass Safety Net. \n-Getting health insurance
        does not warrant a public charge, and thus does not inhibit your ability to apply/get
        citizenship, nor does it affect your immigrant status. \n\n For a factsheet with all of this
        information and more click
        <a href="ability to apply/get citizenship, nor does it affect your immigrant status">here</a>.
        \n\n Want more information about the availability of health insurance, specifically in
        Massachusetts? Visit <a href="https://www.hcfama.org/immigrant-health">Healthcare for All</a>
        \n Want to start applying for Healthcare? Start with the
        <a href="https://www.mahealthconnector.org/">Mass Health Connector Portal</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsHealthcareSpecialConcernsContent">There are a variety of services provided by
        the state of Massachusetts for groups which may have specialized medical needs, both
        physical and mental. These groups include: \n-Women, particularly mothers to young children
        and infants \n-Victims of domestic violence \n-Victims of Trafficking \n-Victims of assault
        and/or abuse. \n\n Information about all of these specialized services can be found at the
        bottom of <a href="https://refugeeswelcomehome.org/refugee-health-care/">this webpage</a>.
    </string>

    <string name="lawsPublicChargePageOverviewStr">Public charge is the law that prevents people who
        are likely to become a government expense from becoming citizens of the United States. The
        expenses which fall under public charge are cash assistance for income maintenance (such as
        SSI and TANF) and institutionalization for long term care. If it is determined that an
        non-citizen either constitutes a public charge or is likely to do so, they will lose their
        eligibility to become a lawful citizen. \n\nSome important notes about public charge\n
        -Public charge does not apply to all immigrant groups\n-Not all welfare programs count
        towards public charge\n-This being said, many of the immigrants who can be affected by
        public charge will not be eligible for the programs which are considered a public charge\n
        -There are considerations outside of the welfare services designated in above sections which
        are used to determine if an individual warrants a public charge including income, health
        status, age, family size, education, etc. \n\nFor a factsheet with the complete information
        from Healthcare for All, Massachusetts, click
        <a href="https://www.hcfama.org/sites/default/files/hcfa_public_charge_consumer_handout_after_scotus_decision.pdf">here</a>.
        \nFor a secondary factsheet from the National Immigration Law Center, click
        <a href="https://www.nilc.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/public-charge-overview-2013-10-01.pdf">here</a>.
    </string>


    <string name="transportationMenuOverviewStr">The MBTA (Massachusetts Bay Transportation
        Authority) is the association which is responsible for a collection of public transportation
        services which are offered in the Massachusetts area. The services are broken down based on
        the type of transportation provided, the region which it is available for, fees,
        accessibility, etc. Select a button below for more information:
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalOverviewStr">Transportation systems in the Greater
        Boston Area:
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayOverviewStr">The subway, or occasionally simply
        referred to as the “T” is a group of underground trains which travel specifically within the
        greater Boston area. The T is composed of 4 major lines: Red, Orange, Green, and Blue, but
        all of these lines do connect to each other, allowing for travel across all parts of the
        area. For a general guide on using the subway, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/guides/subway-guide">here.</a>
        For more specific information see below:</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwaySchedulesContent"> In general, the subway trains
        run every day from 5am to 1am, with more frequent trips during general commute times
        (Weekdays 6:30-9am and 3:30-6:30pm). For more information on where the subway stations are
        as well a a complete schedule and map, click <a href="https://www.mbta.com/schedules/subway">
            here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayFaresContent">The are a variety of ways that the
        fees for using the T can be paid:\n-One Way Fare: Pay one price for a trip from location to
        destination, even if you have to switch lines during the trip. <b>$2.90</b>\n-Charlie Card:
        A rechargeable card for paying for one way fares. Using the Charlie Card reduces the price
        of the one way fare from $2.90 to <b>$2.40</b>\n-Daily/Weekly/Monthly LinkPass: If you plan
        on using the T many times in a day, month, or week, you can purchase a LinkPass, which
        allows for unlimited travel for the designated time period. Price varies based on how long
        the ticket is valid for \n\n For the complete information about fares including where and
        when tickets can be purchased, click <a href="https://www.mbta.com/fares/subway-fares">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayEtiquetteContent">There are a variety of dos and
        don’ts that ought to be followed while using the T. Some of these include:\n-Let passengers
        exit before trying to enter\n-Only take up one seat\n-Place all personal items, including
        backpacks, securely on the floor\n-Take notice of the differences between what is allowed
        during rush hour and off peak times. \n\n For a complete list of T etiquette, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/rider-etiquette">here</a>
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayAccessibilityContent">If mobility is a concern,
        there are some measures in place to try to assist you with that. The majority of the
        underground T stops as well as some of the above ground trolly stops are handicap accessible
        to those using wheelchairs. In addition the MBTA has a
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/trip-planner">trip planner</a> that you can use in order to
        plan an accessible trip. For further information click
        <a href="https://mbta.com/accessibility/trip-planning">here</a>
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalSubwayLanguageServicesContent">Riders should be able to
        use the T regardless of their ability to understand English. Translation and interpretation
        measures have been put into place to ensure that this is possible. For information click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/language-services">here</a>. In addition, you can call
        Customer Support at <a href="tel:+16172223200">(617)222-3200</a>. They have access to
        interpretation services in over 160 languages, and can provide translations of web pages,
        documents, brochures and more.
    </string>

    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerrySchedulesContent">In general, ferry service is available
        from 6am to 11pm throughout the week, however the exact schedule changes depending on the
        season. Ferries are most frequent during peak travel times, weekdays in the morning and
        afternoon. For full schedule click <a href="https://www.mbta.com/schedules/ferry">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryFaresContent">The are a variety of ways that the fees for
        using the ferry can be paid:\n-Ferry One-Way: <b>$3.70 - $9.75</b> (price varies based on
        the route taken)\n-Unlimited use Monthly Pass: <b>$90.00 - $329.00</b>\n\nVisit
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/fares/ferry">here</a> to  enter specific locations and get a
        price for the trip.\n\n Ferry tickets can be purchased with the app mTicket, at Fare Vending
        Machines, Ticket Booths, and online at
        <a hrerf="https://commerce.mbta.com/Passes/">the MBTA website</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDocksContent">Every MBTA ferry terminal is marked with
        a T sign and with its MBTA identification name (Glory, Champion, Lightning, Flying Cloud, Rita,
        and Rookie). Parking varies from dock to dock. If you need assistance, MBTA staff may be
        available at terminals and docks or you can call Customer Support at
        <a href="tel:+16172223200">(617)222-3200</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDurringtheTripHeading1">Wifi</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDurringtheTripContent1">Free WiFi is available on
        some of the Hingham/Hull ferries but is unavailable on the Charlestown ferry.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDurringtheTripHeading2">Food and Beverages</string>
    <string name="transportationStayingLocalFerryDurringtheTripContent2">Snacks and beverages
        (alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks) are available on these ferries. Both cash and credit
        are accepted.
    </string>

    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailOverviewStr">The commuter rail offers easy
        connections between Boston and surrounding communities
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailSchedulesContent">MBTA Commuter Rail connects
        communities in eastern Massachusetts and Rhode Island to downtown Boston, with 137 stops
        throughout the region. There are 12 routes that run 7 days a week. Special service to
        Gillette Stadium from Boston and Providence for sporting events and concerts is included. To
        see all of the Commuter Rail routes click
        <a href="https://cdn.mbta.com/sites/default/files/maps/2019-09-18-commuter-rail-map-v34.pdf">here</a>.
        \n\nEvery Commuter Rail route runs on its own set timetable, but in general service begins
        at 5 AM and ends at 1 AM at many stops. Service is more frequent during peak travel times:
        Monday through Friday, 7-9 AM and 4-7 PM. To see the full Commuter Rail schedule, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/schedules/commuter-rail">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailFaresContent">As with most MBTA transportation,
        there are a variety of ways that the fee required to use the service can be paid:\n-One-way
        or round-trip tickets are recommended if you do not use the Commuter Rail frequently. One
        way tickets cost <b>$2.40 - $13.25</b> (price varies on how far you are traveling) and there
        is no discount for purchasing round-trip tickets.\n10-ride passes are recommended if you
        plan on using the Commuter Rail occasionally over the course of a couple weeks/n-Monthly
        passes are recommended for daily commuters and are valid for unlimited trips during 1
        calendar month.\n\nTickets can be purchased at a variety of different locations, including:
        \n-On-site fare vending machines\n-Ticket windows\n-Some retail sales Locations
        \n-Occasionally, on board the train (although an extra fee may be required, and this service
        is not always available).
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsHeading1">Parking</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsContent1">Some Commuter Rail
        stations have parking. To check if a station has parking, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/stops/commuter-rail">here</a>; all stations marked with a “P”
        have available parking.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsHeading2">Boarding the Train</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsContent2">At single-platform
        stations, there is only one location to get on the train. At multiple-platform stations,
        platforms will be numbered or lettered and train details will be posted on digital signs
        several minutes before arrival. At large stations, there will be a departure board in the
        main terminal with every train’s platform number, however hese may not be available until a
        few minutes before the train arrives.</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsHeading3">Restrooms</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsContent3">Large stations have
        public restrooms but not all stations have public restrooms. Restrooms are available on the
        Commuter Rail trains themselves; they are located at the ends of some cars.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsHeading4">Need Assistance?</string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailNavigatingStationsContent4">If assistance is
        needed, at North, South, and Back Bay stations, staff are available from 5:30 AM - 12 AM
        Monday through Friday and 7 AM - 11 PM on weekends and holidays. At other stations staff
        members may be available on a limited basis. Call Customer Support at <a href="tel:+16172223200">(617)222-3200</a>
        if assistance is needed.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailOntheTrainContent">Some general notes about
        riding the Commuter Rail:\n-Free WiFi is available on some Commuter Rail trains, look for
        the WiFi logos in enabled cars.\n-During peak travel times, (Mon-Fri, 7-9 AM and 4-7 PM),
        the car that is closest to the engine is a designated “Quiet Car”. Customers in this car are
        asked to avoid loud conversations, talking on their phones, and use headphones to listen to
        music or watch videos.\n-Alcoholic drinks are <b>not</b> allowed on the Commuter Rail, but
        non-alcoholic drinks are.\n-Bikes are allowed on the Commuter Rail <b>during off-peak travel
            times only</b>.\n-On train restrooms are located at the ends of some cars.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationGoingFarCommuterRailAccessibilityContent">Most Commuter Rail stations are
        accessible to people with disabilities. To check if a particular station is handicap
        accessible, check <a href="https://www.mbta.com/stops/commuter-rail">here</a>; the stations
        marked with a wheelchair symbol are accessible to individuals with disabilities.\n\n
        Individuals with disabilities and seniors are eligible to travel on the Commuter Rail for
        half the price of a standard one-way fare.</string>

    <string name="transportationBusScheduleContent">MBTA buses connect neighborhoods in Greater Boston with
        each other and offer service to many surrounding cities and towns. The service area includes
        more than 170 routes that run between 5-7 days a week. Throughout the region there are 8,000
        stops. To see a full system map click
        <a href="https://cdn.mbta.com/sites/default/files/maps/2020-03-15-mbta-system-map-full.pdf">here</a>.
        \n\nEvery bus route has its own schedule with a majority of the routes running between 5 AM
        and 1 AM. There are some routes that run between 1 AM and 5 AM. To see all bus schedules go
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/schedules/bus">here</a>\n\nLocal Buses make stops within
        Boston while Outer Express Buses travel further out connecting some cities with the Boston
        area.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationBusFaresContent">-Local bus service one-way is <b>$1.70</b> with a
        CharlieCard and <b>$2.00</b> with a CharlieTicker or cash. To learn more about CharlieCards and
        CharlieTickets, click <a href="https://www.mbta.com/fares/charliecard">here</a>\n-Inner
        Express service one-way is <b>$4.25</b> with a CharlieCard and <b>$5.25</b> with a
        2CharlieTicket or cash.\n-Outer Express service one-way is <b>$5.25</b> with a CharlieCard
        and <b>$7.00</b> with a CharlieTicket or cash.\n-A 1-Day Pass is <b>$12.75</b> and includes
        unlimited travel for 24 hours on Local Buses and the subway.\n-A 2-Day Pass is <b>$22.50</b>
        and includes unlimited travel for a week on Local Buses and the subway.\n-A Local Bus
        Monthly Pass costs <b>$55.00</b>.\n-A Monthly LinkPass (travel on Local Buses and subway)
        costs <b>$90.00</b>.\n-An Outer Express Bus Monthly Pass costs <b>$168.00</b>\n\nTickets can
        be bought at Fare Vending Machines, some Retail Sales locations, on board the bus, or online
        <a href="https://charliecard.mbta.com/CharlieCardWebProgram/pages/charlieCardCenter.jsf">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationBusEtiquetteContent">There are a few general rules that all riders
        should follow while using MBTA buses:\n-Let passengers exit the bus before trying to board
        the bus, especially during rush hour.\n-When boarding, move all the way into the vehicle to
        create space for the other passengers.\n-Only take up 1 seat. If you have a seat and no more
        are available, offer your seat to seniors, pregnant women, and people with disabilities.
        \n-Take off your backpack, and keep large personal items on the floor and out of the way.
        \n-Service animals are allowed at all times. Non-service dogs are not allowed during peak
        hours (Mon - Fri, 7 AM - 9 AM and 4 AM - 6:30 PM). Dogs should be on a leash and cannot take
        up a seat as there is room to lay down under the seats. Smaller animals should be kept in
        pet carriers.\n-All MBTA buses that are non-electric have bike racks that can hold 2
        conventional bikes.\n-All stops and transfer points are announced automatically and
        displayed on a screen that is at the front of the bus.\n-To request a stop press the yellow
        or gray strips that are near the windows of the bus, or the red “Stop” buttons that are on
        the vertical handrails.\n-In case of an emergency call 911 or the Transit Police at
        <a href="tel:+16172221212">(617)222-1212</a>.
    </string>

    <string name="transportationAccessibilityOverview">If a user is unable to utilize the other
        forms of MBTA transportation due to a disability, they may be eligible to utilize the
        MBTA\'s RIDE service. Please note that in order to use the RIDE, you must be a pre-certified
        RIDE customer.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityHeading1">Who can use the RIDE?</string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityContent1">-Both people with physical disabilities as
        well as temporary mobility impairments caused by injury may be eligible for the RIDE, as the
        RIDE is a safety-net service, and thus eligibility is determined on the basis of inability
        to use other forms of public transportation.\n-Both Boston area residents and visitors to
        the Boston area can become certified RIDE users. For more information about using the RIDE
        as a visitor, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/accessibility/the-ride/the-ride-paratransit-visitors">here</a>.
        \n-All certified RIDE customers are allowed to bring their Personal Care Attendant (PCA) on
        the RIDE with them free of charge. If space is available, they can also bring one guest at
        standard RIDE rates.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityHeading2">How to apply for a RIDE certification</string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityContent2">A ride certification can be obtained for
        eligible individuals by following these 3 steps:\n-1. Call the RIDE eligibility center (TREC)
        at <a href="tel:+16173372727">(617)337-2727</a> to set up an appointment for your
        interview\n2. Complete an interview at the TREC where you can tell a Mobility Coordinator
        about yourself and your circumstances which make using the RIDE a necessity.\n3. For more
        details on how to apply for a RIDE certification, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/accessibility/the-ride/how-apply-the-ride">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityHeading3">RIDE user policies</string>
    <string name="transportationAccessibilityContent3">If you are a certified RIDE user, click
        <a href="https://www.mbta.com/accessibility/the-ride/the-ride-policies">here</a> to see the
        general rules and etiquette to follow while using the RIDE.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
